The collaboration deal is here!
Let SD48 be revealed in the game as well!
SD48 is now complete!
Before I let you take a quick look at it, I'd like to say a few words first about how we feel about it...
How do you like it?
This one's a joke, this one's a summary
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm not kidding!
Humor
I don't know if I'll ever be one again.
I really don't.
I can't imagine.
They're all so good. They're all so good.
I'm sure you're all wondering... how it all turned out.
I'm sure you're wondering, but actually...
We had a rough design for all of them, and actually, one part from each of your illustrations was adopted.
What? Which corner? You want to see it, don't you?
Before I show you, here's a quiz.
Guess which one and write it down again.
If you can answer all five correctly.
I'll be chosen as one of the 100 most famous people on the food log.
A cake from a popular pastry store.
Heh.
Wow!
It's so soft and juicy!
I've decided not to have this beautiful cake, so who'll go for it?
I have nothing but boo-boo's and I want to go, Mr. Michisaki.
Please, Mr. Michisaki.
Remember what I told you last time? Remember?
Adopt it.
Where is it, Rinri-chan?
I think I presented the shape of the boat.
Mainly.
When I presented it.
I didn't have this idea.
You've done a great job.
I think the president is very concerned about the turnout.
I think the president was very concerned about the turnout and the young people, and he was very concerned about the people.
I was asking him why he was so interested in the bar and what was in it.
I only said "feet" and he said it's all about taste... and I thought it was funny that he thought I had feet.
I'm funny.
I'm sorry, just for a second.
I'm sorry, it's just for a moment... but I'll tell you what's funny and what's not... whether it has a face or not.
I'm not sure if I have a face or a foot in there.
I'm not really sure if there's a foot in there, or if there's a logo on the st-4t floor, or if there's skin.
I'm looking at it from a third-person perspective, and it's wide open.
Oh, my God!
It's amazing... but there's no feet.
But there was no foot!
I got this... This was there.
There it is?
Really?
Which is it?
I think I found this.
I think I saw some wings.
Did it have wings?
I don't think it had wings.
I don't think so.
I don't know. I don't think there were any wings like a third person.
I don't know.
What did you think? Like the big three?
No, not at all.
Red and brown, like chocolate.
I don't know.
It was bluish.
Like the big three.
It's kind of chocolatey.
There was something like hairs.
The base was soroha ahhhh! AHH...  Three! More than half! More than half! [Question]
Then show us the illustrations, please!
Yes! Yes!
Let's see, the base is Soraha's ship
And Imamura's propeller.
Saayan's face.
Momochan's flag
Rinetan's scales
Yay! What kind of boat did you end up with? I will ask Mr. Murakami to tell us about the front and development pattern used this time. Please do.
Then, I'd like to go take a look immediately.
Oh no, wait, wait, wait!Oh, no. Wait, wait, wait.
Did I see it wrong?
Steve 48's.
Wow, this is gonna be fun.
Oh, ever.
Cool face.
Oh, hey.
You have a face.
You do have a face.
Do you have a cell?
What? You have a cell.
There's a cell.
There's a cell!
Get out of the cell. Look! Silver!
What do you think was the hardest part of the project?
I was working on a croissant for the SDF Teelette.
I had to create a shape and line that I could remember.
We worked on the colors and the lines together.
That's what I'm talking about here.
I'm sure you're right.
This is the basic tip of the STL treatment.
Wow! Thank you.
Like a line.
Oh, really? I miss it!
The squadron is me now.
Me?
It's the back.
Me? Me?
Oh! I'm so happy! I did it!
It was hard for me to imagine it horizontally, so it ended up vertically.
Wow! It's so cool!
It's so cool!
So, you are on the stairs. I will be on the stage.
Wow! Wow!
On stage?
Egg!
On stage! A stage!
This is a snubbelina!
Oh, almost!
Almost there, too.
I'll get it.
And here's the rest.
Oki Tomosho of Otomui
YouTube Idol
Chia
Whose illustrations
Who's illustrations were easiest to incorporate? Whose illustration was easiest to incorporate?
What was the easiest to incorporate?
The tsunami for the main hall of the mountain.
It was very catchy and cute,
He signed all of them.
I'm so happy!
That's great!
Is the animation already in pieces?
Oh, it's all in pieces.
What part of the boat was the hardest to get into?
You want to call it a thread?
Sweat
I'm not sure if we can include this as a ship, but it's quite interesting.
It was a foot.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
It's also a hand.
So you're saying you're raising a child now?
Yes, six of a kind.
That's a lot.
Tsunamelli's right.
Hatter.
Hatterdas, so six kinds? Tsunamili was right, wasn't it? Hatter was right.
Yes, sir.
Hata.
Two.
Oh, there it is.
Dodora propeller? Propeller?
Propeller.
I see.
Dodora propeller.Dodrapella.
Maybe, but if you have a little big grain
Oh, wow.
Hata, hata
You're hurting my hand.
Uh, two?
Oh, that's too bad.
Oh, that's too bad, that's too bad, that's too bad.
That's a shame.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid you can't beat the cake.
As for this cake.
Let's let Murakami-san eat it.
Murakami-san.
Why me?
You want to eat it.
Oh, no!
Look closer.
It's so shiny!
What's with the plate style?
Oh, it looks like that.
Eh, it's still super cute!
It's kind of shiny like this
It's like Orkami!
Let's give it to him!
Let's give it to him already!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
The top part looks delicious.
I love it.
But you know what?
You made it.
I want to eat it most of all.
If it's fun, I'll give it to you.
It's hard to eat, isn't it?
Not at all.
I'll have a lot of it.
Wow!
What do you think?
It's very rich.
Wow.
That's good.
Now, here's test number two.
The peepaw test.
I've already given it one more shot, but...
I'm going to go with that Sky Profiles gameplay.
Yes, sir.
In the Time Talk series that we just did...
Anzu, I'd like you to use No. 2 for now.
I'm so glad.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
He got away!
Run, run, run, run! Run, run, run! He's getting away!
You attacked me.
Okay.
Eight on my side.
If you find this video interesting.
please give it a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
Watch the next video!